# **Anton Mitrofanov**

C# Sr. Software Engineer at Cian

Moscow, Russia linkedin.com/in/anton-mitrofanov milording@gmail.com +7 926 384-23-05 I am a product-minded software engineer with over 6 years experience in C# My main focus is developing quality products, including the whole process from discussing the details with the product team to support in production. I don't do tasking, but solving business problems, the result of which can be planned and measured. I love working with a team, holding Agile meetings, engaging the team in the product and improving processes of development

## Work Experience

#### C# Sr. Software Engineer

Cian

Jan 2020 - Current

Top-1(15+ mln MAU) real estate search platform in Russia

- Lead a product growth team of 5 people. The team launched 20+ A/B tests every month leading to significant (+37%) increases in sign-ups and activation
- Reduced the support team's moderation efforts by 4 times by automating the process leading to faster customer onboarding
- Developed a subscription payment system that processed thousands payments
- · Facilitated team retrospective, planning and grooming meetings
- Interviewed 30+ engineers

## C# Software Engineer

golama

Apr 2018 - Jan 2020

Platform for ordering groceries from Moscow stores

- Developed a bot that answered user questions, which reduced the manual work of the support team
- Implemented Apple Pay & Google Pay that increased the number of transactions by up to 44% and speeded up the checkout process
- Implemented dynamic delivery pricing which expanded delivery options in terms of time and price, that significantly increased revenue

#### C# Software Engineer

Sberbank-Technology

Apr 2017 - Apr 2018

- · Offered and developed the architecture for UI tests that covered more than 80% of manual testing
- Developed custom controls for image cropping
- Developed the integration with cellular providers

#### C# Software Engineer

**Todoist** 

Jun 2016 - Dec 2016

- · Developed custom controls, graphs and navigation flows that allowed us to solve UX problems we had
- Refactoring and optimizing issues with synchronization

#### C# Software Engineer

Hyperboloid

Feb 2015 - Feb 2016

Developed 2 applications:

- 1. ShowJet streaming service with great offline capabilities and tons of non-trivial custom controls
- 2. Strelka application for managing Moscow public transport cards

Developed a Windows Phone application which recognized business cards by capturing an image, saving data to SQLite, sync with cloud and contact list

• Runtime Component for intermediate code between C++ engine and C#

#### Skills -

Languages & Tools C#, Python, F#, SQL, TypeScript, Azure, AWS, Grafana, Kibana, Jenkins,

Docker

Databases PostgreSQL, Microsoft SQL Server, MongoDB, EF Core, Dapper

Managment Agile, Scrum, Kanban, Product Roadmap, Airtable, Jira

### Education

BSc Computer Science National Research University of Electronic Technology 2013 - 2017

## Languages

Russian Native

**English** Advanced

**Dutch** Intermediate